<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ens on TravenUp</title>
    <link>http://www.travenup.com/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ens on TravenUp</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 11:36:37 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://www.travenup.com/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips</title>
      <link>http://www.travenup.com/en/help/tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 11:36:37 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.travenup.com/en/help/tips/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About TravenUp</title>
      <link>http://www.travenup.com/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 11:36:29 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.travenup.com/en/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;about-travenup:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;About TravenUp&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At TravenUp Atividades de Internet Ltda. (“TravenUp”, “we” or “us”), we recognize that earning and retaining your trust is the most important thing we do as a business. Prote cting your privacy is a responsibility we take very seriously.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TravenUp provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of www.TravenUp.com (the “Site”) and any related applications (the “Application” or “App”) and otherwise, through the Service. This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through the Service. This Privacy Policy does not address, and we are not responsible for, the privacy, information or other practices of any third party, including any third-party distribution partners, suppliers and tour operators, and any third party operating any site to which our website or App contain a link.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your information may be transferred to - and maintained on - computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside Brazil and choose to provide information to us, Travenup transfers personal information to Brazil and processes it there. Your consent to this privacy policy followed by your submission of such information on&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>