<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ens on TravenUp</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ens on TravenUp</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 11:36:37 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/help/tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 11:36:37 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/help/tips/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;tips:e7ca16f375e6c22df64705b42852662b&#34;&gt;Tips&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-simple-guide-to-a-successful-service:e7ca16f375e6c22df64705b42852662b&#34;&gt;A Simple Guide to a successful service!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;for-travelers:e7ca16f375e6c22df64705b42852662b&#34;&gt;For Travelers&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hi &lt;strong&gt;Traveler,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Before start your travel, communicate with the Insider to confirm the booked time and dates, and if something unexpected happens, please communicate TravenUp and the Insider.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be respectful to your local insider, an experience begins in meeting new people.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unexpected Gests: Your booking is confirmed for a certain number of people, confirm in advance with the local Insider if you can bring additional people.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leave your feedback to the local Insider. They appreciate it very much, and so do we!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;for-insiders:e7ca16f375e6c22df64705b42852662b&#34;&gt;For Insiders&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hi &lt;strong&gt;Local Insider,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be transparent, tell exactly what is your listing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be clear about price, what is included or not.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Set hour, date and exact place. Welcome with a big smile!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Respond promptly exchanged menssages about booking requests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Booking is a commitment. Travelers expect an unforgettable service. In emergencies contact TravenUp.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If something goes wrong inadvertently, try to remedy the situation. Be a hero to your traveler!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About TravenUp</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 11:36:29 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;about-travenup:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;About TravenUp&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Local experiences are the most enriching and cool!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We connect people who have expertise in travel services and experiences with those who are looking for these experices and services. Travelers can build real connections with local Insiders (suppliers of these services and experiences), gain access to distinctive and unique sites and condct an immersion in the culture of the destination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We provide the Traveler with the expertise, taste and local secrets and bring to the local Insiders the pleasure to share their knowledge and time, and of course, being paid for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are TravenUp! A place to find travel experiences and services, connecting people.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/privacy/privacy_policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 10:48:36 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/privacy/privacy_policy/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;privacy-policy:ba8e20cb6e739a50bc3b05dfc391e82b&#34;&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At TravenUp Atividades de Internet Ltda. (“TravenUp”, “we” or “us”), we recognize that earning and retaining your trust is the most important thing we do as a business. Protecting your privacy is a responsibility we take very seriously.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TravenUp provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of www.TravenUp.com (the “Site”) and any related applications (the “Application” or “App”) and otherwise, through the Service. This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through the Service. This Privacy Policy does not address, and we are not responsible for, the privacy, information or other practices of any third party, including any third-party distribution partners, suppliers and tour operators, and any third party operating any site to which our website or App contain a link.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your information may be transferred to - and maintained on - computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside Brazil and choose to provide information to us, TravenUp transfers personal information to Brazil and processes it there. Your consent to this privacy policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;contents:ba8e20cb6e739a50bc3b05dfc391e82b&#34;&gt;Contents&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Who We Are&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What Information Do We Collect?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cookies, and How We Use Them&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How We Use Your Personal Information&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Email Communications You Can Expect to Receive from TravenUp&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Listing, Partners and Suppliers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our Security and Storage Measures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Changes to Our Privacy Policy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contacting Us&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;who-we-are:ba8e20cb6e739a50bc3b05dfc391e82b&#34;&gt;Who We Are&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TravenUp is an internet platform. We provide an environment where Suppliers and Travelers make a connection. Travelers can search for a specific Service, Supplier or Insider, and they may communicate each other, make deals, receive services and make payments. The TravenUp platform is not the supplier of the Travelers services, TravenUp platform is only the place where this business happen, we provide all infra-structure technology for both, suppliers, as we call “insiders” and Travelers that are their &amp;ldquo;customers&amp;rdquo; to interact each other. It is important that each and every Traveler evaluate the insider relevance, competence and reviews before buy any chosen service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-information-do-we-collect:ba8e20cb6e739a50bc3b05dfc391e82b&#34;&gt;What Information Do We Collect?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We collect Personal Information in connection with our registration form to join the Service and other information that does not identify you personally, such as gender, country of residence and other demographic information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you register with us through the Service and become a Member and when you choose to post a Listing or book a Service, or when you wish to contact another Member, we will ask you for personally identifiable information. This refers to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you (“Identity Information”). Identity Information includes, but is not limited to, your name, phone number, email address, social security number (SSN), fiscal or government-issued identification card, and home postal address, but does not include your credit card number or billing information. In order to process some of your transactions through the Service, we may also ask for your credit card number and other billing information (“Billing Information”) (Identity Information and Billing Information together, “Personal Information”). If the address associated with a Listing you post matches that of your credit card billing address, that address would be considered Identity Information. Some Personal Information may be required, like your name and email address, and other Personal Information may be optional. We use your Personal Information to provide the Service and administer your inquiries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;cookies-and-how-we-use-them:ba8e20cb6e739a50bc3b05dfc391e82b&#34;&gt;Cookies, and How We Use Them&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Cookies&amp;rdquo; are pieces of information that are stored by your web browser on your computer&amp;rsquo;s hard disk, for record-keeping purposes. Cookies in and of themselves only identify your computer; they do not personally identify you. As used in this policy, the terms “using” and “processing” information include using cookies on a computer, subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or handling information in any way, including, but not limited to collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within our organization or among our affiliates within Brazil or internationally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We may also use third-party advertising companies to serve ads while you are visiting our websites and we permit these companies to place and access their own cookies on your computer in the course of serving advertisements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-we-use-your-personal-information:ba8e20cb6e739a50bc3b05dfc391e82b&#34;&gt;How We Use Your Personal Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We may use your personal information in the following ways:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To provide you with the information you request about our services.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To send you email marketing messages and information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To fulfill your bookings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To confirm your purchases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To ensure you are correctly billed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To measure and track demographic details about our customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To target content on our website to more closely match your interests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To target the appropriate content for email marketing messages to better match your interests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may also be permitted to register to join by logging into online accounts you may have with third party service providers (“SNS”) (e.g. Facebook); each such account, a “Third Party Account”, via the Service as described below. As part of the functionality of the Service, you may link your TravenUp Account with Third Party Accounts, by either: (i) providing your Third Party Account login information to TravenUp through the Service; or (ii) allowing TravenUp to access your Third Party Account, as is permitted under the applicable terms and conditions that govern your use of each Third Party Account. You represent that you are entitled to disclose your Third Party Account login information to TravenUp and/or grant TravenUp access to your Third Party Account (including, but not limited to, for use for the purposes described herein), without breach by you of any of the terms and conditions that govern your use of the applicable Third Party Account and without obligating TravenUp to pay any fees or making TravenUp subject to any usage limitations imposed by the applicable SNS. If you decide to register by logging into a Third Party Account via the Service, we will obtain the Personal Information you have provided to the applicable SNS (such as your “real” name, email address, profile picture, names of SNS friends, names of SNS groups to which you belong, other information you make publicly available via the applicable SNS and/or other information you authorize TravenUp to access by authorizing the SNS to provide such information) from your Third Party Accounts and use that information to create your TravenUp Account and TravenUp Account profile page and you will become a Member. Depending on the Third Party Accounts you choose and subject to the privacy settings that you have set in such Third Party Accounts, you understand that by granting us access to the Third Party Accounts, we will access, make available and store (if applicable and as permitted by the SNS and authorized by you) the information in your Third Party Accounts so that it is available on and through your TravenUp Account on the Service. If there is information about your “friends” or people with whom you are associated in your Third Party Account, the information we obtain about those “friends” or people with whom you are associated, may also depend on the privacy settings such people have with the applicable SNS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;email-communications-you-can-expect-to-receive-from-travenup:ba8e20cb6e739a50bc3b05dfc391e82b&#34;&gt;Email Communications You Can Expect to Receive from TravenUp&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We may send to you marketing emails with information about TravenUp deals and other special promotions that we believe that you will find valuable, interesting or informative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of the Service, TravenUp Users may communicate with TravenUp Members through the Service. Where TravenUp Users have selected the option of adding one or more email addresses to an online form, the message they create in the corresponding template may be sent from TravenUp to those email addresses on their behalf. If so, such email addresses will be used only for the purpose of sending the email communication to the addressee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Site and Application may contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs), which would be used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how the Service is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This would allow us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-security-and-storage-measures:ba8e20cb6e739a50bc3b05dfc391e82b&#34;&gt;Our Security and Storage Measures&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you visit our site or app, whether as a Member or a non-registered user just browsing (any of these, a “TravenUp User”), our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer&amp;rsquo;s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type or the webpage you were visiting before you came to the Service, pages of the Service that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on the site or app, access times and dates, and other statistics. We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the Service and for the Service’s technical administration, to increase the Service’s functionality and user-friendliness, and to better tailor the Service to our visitors&amp;rsquo; and users’ needs. We also use this information to verify that visitors to and users of the Service meet the criteria required to process their requests. We do not treat Log Data as Personal Information or use it in association with other Personal Information, though we may aggregate, analyze and evaluate such information for the same purposes as stated above regarding other Non-Identifying Information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Identity theft and the practice currently known as “phishing” are of great concern to TravenUp. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your TravenUp Account ID, login password, or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you create a TravenUp Account, we will set up a TravenUp Account profile page for you. Your TravenUp Account profile page will include your first name and last initial. You can select the other items of Personal Information that you wish to be included in your TravenUp Account profile page – including, but not limited to, a profile picture. We will display your Profile Information in your TravenUp Account profile page publicly via the Service, and, with your prior permission, on third party sites. Any information you choose to provide as part of your Profile Information will be publicly visible to all TravenUp Users and consequently should reflect how much you want other TravenUp Users to know about you. We recommend that you guard your anonymity and sensitive information and we encourage members to think carefully about what information about themselves they disclose in their profile pages. You can review and revise your Profile Information at any time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;listing-partners-and-suppliers:ba8e20cb6e739a50bc3b05dfc391e82b&#34;&gt;Listing, Partners and Suppliers&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you post a Listing, we may publish that Listing publicly via the Service and may enable third parties to publish your Listing on their websites through the use of an HTML “widget”. We may also display the geographical location of your Listing in the form of a map so that potential Travelers can see the general area and neighborhood of your Listing, but the actual street address will not be disclosed until you enter into a confirmed transaction with another Member. If you request to make a booking via the Service, TravenUp may share the following information about you with the applicable Insider: your first and last name and a link to your TravenUp Account profile page. All of this information will enable the Insider to decide whether to confirm or reject your booking. When a Insider confirms a booking we may share pieces of the Insider’s Identify Information, including, but not limited to, full name, phone number, the Experience’s starting address and the Insider’s email address, with the applicable Traveler selected by the Insider and we may share pieces of the Traveler’s Identify Information with the Insider, including, but not limited to, full name, phone number and email address, so that the Traveler and Insider may contact one another directly. In no event is a Traveler&amp;rsquo;s Billing Information shared with an Insider.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We may share aggregated information that does not identify you personally and we may otherwise disclose Non-Identifying Information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not identify you personally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Site and Application-related services (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, web analytics, fraud detection services relating to the activity of TravenUp Users and improvement of the Service&amp;rsquo;s features) or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. These third parties may have access to your Personal Information; if they do, this access is only so that they may perform these tasks on our behalf and they are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose. You can, at any time, opt out of receiving such communications. Third party vendors, like Google, may use cookies to serve ads based on a TravenUp User&amp;rsquo;s prior visits to TravenUp. You can disable these specific cookies that track prior visits for the sake of follow-up advertising by opting out at &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/&#34;&gt;http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TravenUp cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of TravenUp or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials and to our insurance services providers as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to protect the property and rights of TravenUp or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Site and Application may contain links to other websites. If you choose to visit an advertiser by “clicking on” a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third party&amp;rsquo;s website. The fact that we link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other websites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With your consent we may post your testimonial on the Service along with your name. If you want your testimonial removed please contact us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Service is not directed to individuals under 18. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 18. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us. If we become aware that a child under 18 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;changes-to-our-privacy-policy:ba8e20cb6e739a50bc3b05dfc391e82b&#34;&gt;Changes to Our Privacy Policy&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TravenUp may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;contacting-us:ba8e20cb6e739a50bc3b05dfc391e82b&#34;&gt;Contacting Us&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at support@TravenUp.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All Members may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information in their registration profile by contacting us at support@TravenUp.com or editing the relevant part of their profile. If you would like us to cancel your TravenUp Account, please contact us and we will attempt to accommodate your request if we do not have any legal obligation or a legitimate business reason to retain the information contained in your TravenUp Account. Please note that, if you cancel your TravenUp Account, any reviews you have posted via the Service will remain publicly viewable via the Service.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>